--- PAGE 1 ---
Welcome to VHXII !
Opening Ceremony
--- PAGE 2 ---
Schedule
Tracks
Prizes
Tech Together MeetUp
Our Sponsors
MLH
Agenda

--- PAGE 3 ---
Key Websites
h t t p s : / / v a n d y h a c k s . o r g /
h t t p : / / v a n d y h a c k s - x i i . d e v p o s t . c o m
h t t p s : / / d i s c o r d . c o m /

--- PAGE 4 ---
Time Event
7:45 AM û 9:15 AM Registration / Check-In
9:15 AM û 10:30 AM Opening Ceremony
10:45 AM û 11:15 AM MLH Workshop 1
11:30 AM Hackathon Begins
~1:00 PM - 2.00 PM Lunch
2:00 PM - 2:30 PM Hackathon Workshop 1
3:00 PM û 3:30 PM MLH Workshop 2
4:00 PM - 5:00 PM Social Event 1- Tech Together MeetUp
5:30 PM - 6:00 PM Hackathon Workshop 2
7:00 PM û 8:00 PM Dinner
8:00 PM û 8:30 PM Social Event 2á
S c h e d u l e  D a y - 1

--- PAGE 5 ---
Weekend Goals
Learn a lot of cool tech 
Build amazing projects 
Share what you learn with fellow hackers 
Have a fun 24 hours 
Maintain a safe environment 
We abide by the Major League Hacking Code of Conduct 

--- PAGE 6 ---
I m p o r t a n t  I n f o r m a t i o n
Hackers are allowed on the first, second,
and third floor of the building. Places
where hackers cannot enter are clearly
labeled with a Do Not Enter sign. All the
allowed areas have been labeled with
ôHackathon Areaö
--- PAGE 7 ---
In Case of Emergency...
E v a c u a t i o n  P l a n :  i n  t h e  e v e n t  o f  a n  e m e r g e n c y ,  h a c k e r s
s h o u l d  u s e  t h e  H i g h l a n d  A v e n u e  f a c i n g  s t a i r w e l l s .
A d d i t i o n a l l y ,  E S B  i s  a  ô h i g h  h a z a r d ö  b u i l d i n g  d u e  t o  t h e
t o x i c  p r o c e s s  c h e m i c a l s  i n  t h e  b u i l d i n g .  I n  t h e  e v e n t  o f
o f  a  c h e m i c a l  r e l e a s e ,  t h e  f i r e  a l a r m  w i l l  g o  o f f  a n d  t h e
l i g h t  s t a c k  ( s e e  b e l o w )  w i l l  i n d i c a t e  t h e  p r o b l e m  ( y o u  w i l l
s e e  t h i s  l i g h t  s t a c k  o n  t h e  g r o u n d  f l o o r  n e x t  t o  t h e
C l e a n r o o m ) .  B a s i c a l l y ,  i f  t h e  b l u e  l i g h t  i s  g o i n g  o f f ,
e v e r y o n e  s h o u l d  l e a v e  t h e  b u i l d i n g  i m m e d i a t e l y .
--- PAGE 8 ---
T r a c k s

--- PAGE 9 ---
Tracks
Health tech ù Build tools that put people in control of
their health.
 E.g. AI diagnostics, mental wellness apps, care
navigation, wearable integrations, health equity.
Startup launchpad ù Build the MVP, the pitch, or the
infrastructure for a working prototype.
E.g. B2B SaaS tools, founder productivity tools,
marketplace ideas, no-code / automation platforms,
pitch deck / design / promo generators.
Capital One Track

--- PAGE 10 ---
S o c i a l  E v e n t s  
A n d  P r i z e s !

--- PAGE 11 ---
Prizes
Best Overall Hack (top project) 
Second Place (runner up)
Third Place
Best Use of AI
Best in Healthcare
Best Startup Idea
Best Design
Capital One Track Prize
Prizes: Amazon Echos, Drones, Projecters, Smart Lamps,  etc. 

--- PAGE 12 ---
M e r c h !

--- PAGE 13 ---
Thank You to Our
Sponsor!
--- PAGE 14 ---

--- PAGE 15 ---
C a r e e r  P a n e l !
--- PAGE 16 ---

--- PAGE 17 ---
M e e t  O u r  M L H  C o a c h ,
D u n n i  D a y o - K a y o d e  ! ! !
--- PAGE 18 ---
Tech Together 
Meet-Up
--- PAGE 19 ---
Please Spend The Next Few
Minutes Finding Teammates
Until Our First Workshop of
The Day held by MLH.

--- PAGE 20 ---
Happy Hacking!!!
